A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  - 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 4
    - Assembly Campaign, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 273)
    - Associates of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 274)
    - Richard Aurelio, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 275)
    - Budgets; Miscellaneous Expenses of Projects, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 276)
    - "Rockefeller New York City Campaign in the Streets", 1966 (Box 22, Folder 277)
    - Campaign Contribution Acknowledgements by Willliam L. Pfeiffer, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 278)
    - Republican Assembly Campaign Handbook, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 279)
    - History File, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 280)
      Lists of 1966 candidates, internal campaign memos.
    - Organization, 1966 March 30 (Box 22, Folder 281)
      Campaign Organization, special groups, estimate of "situation."
    - Campaign Structure, 1966 February 10 (Box 22, Folder 282)
      Memo to NAR from William L. Pfeiffer.
    - Organization Charts, Maps, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 283)
    - "La Follia di New York" (Italian Language Magazine), 1966 October (Box 22, Folder 284)
    - Congressional Liason - Campaign, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 285)
    - Conservative Party, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 286)
    - County Chairmen, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 287)
    - Courts, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 288)
    - Debate - WABC-TV, 1966 October 29 (Box 23, Folder 289)
    - Distribution of Campaign Materials, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 290)
    - Edwards, Deighton - Campaign Expenses, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 291)
    - Election Results, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 292)
    - Estate Tax Attorneys, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 293)
    - Ferenbach, Edwin - Nassau and Suffolk Counties; Reports, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 294)
    - Financial Reports - Friends of Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 295)
    - Fish, Hamilton vs. Alexander Aldrich for Congress, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 296)
    - Fish, Hamilton vs. Alexander Aldrich for Congress, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 297)
    - Foreign Press - Cocktail Party, 1966 October 24 (Box 23, Folder 298)
    - Girard, Mimi - New York City Co-Director, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 299)
    - Glenn, Leonard - Bronx United Republican Club, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 300)
    - Governor's Calendar, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 301)
    - Governor's Club - Invitation to Join to Rodman Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 302)
    - Grimsey, Herbert, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 303)
      Coordinator: Putnam, Rockland, Westchester, Dutchess and Orange Counties.
    - 1962 Campaign Information, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 304)
    - Hampton, Lionel, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 305)
    - Hellmath, James - Memos from Michael Scelsi, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 306)
    - Hilton Hotel Expenses for Friends of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 307)
    - Home Builders - "Builders for the Rockefeller Team", 1966 (Box 24, Folder 308)
    - Independent Committee, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 309)
    - Insurance Committee for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 310)
    - Inter-Group Relations - Jackie Robinson, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 311)
      Budget and Planning.
    - Invitations, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 312)
    - Jones, Nina - Reports, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 313)
    - Katz, Robert - Report on "Self-Mailer", 1966 (Box 24, Folder 314)
    - Endorsements, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 315)
      Labor Endorsement, endorsement by "New York Courier," a black weekly newspaper.
    - Lanigan, Charles T., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 316)
      State Comptroller Candidate, Campaign material and schedules.
    - News Clippings - Lawlay, Games, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 317)
    - Lefkowitz, Louis G. (Attorney General) - Schedule, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 318)
    - Local Assistance Fund - Direct Aid to Counties, 1966 February (Box 24, Folder 319)
    - Lomenzo, John P., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 320)
    - Losee, Thomas R., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 321)
    - Medicaid - Press Release, 1966 October 9 (Box 25, Folder 322)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 323)
      Confidential Memo - "Potential Campaign Changes" and assignments in response to it.
    - Miscellaneous (2), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 324)
    - Nationalities Division - 1964 Election Results, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 325)
    - New York City, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 326)
      New York City Campaign, New York City Income Tax (estimates of revenue), NAR speech honoring Israel's President Shazar.
    - O'Donnell, Harry, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 327)
    - Operation Keyman Summary, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 328)
    - Personnel, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 329)
      Lists, salaries, resumes.
    - Pfeiffer, William, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 330)
    - Pfeiffer, William - Thank you Letters, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 331)
    - Republican State Committee Platform Advisory Committee Hearings, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 332)
    - Polish Division, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 333)
      Correspondence, proposed NAR speech.
    - Pre-Campaign Staff Strategy Meetings, 1966 January-February (Box 26, Folder 334)
    - Radio and TV Appearances, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 335)
    - Registration, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 336)
    - Reid, Fergus III, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 337)
    - Republican State Committee, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 338)
      Membership list, news releases.
    - Republlican State Convention, 1966 September 6 (Box 26, Folder 339)
      Delegates, candidates biographies, speeches.
    - Research Division, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 340)
    - Robinson, Jackie - Memos Re: Negro Vote, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 341)
    - Rockefeller Rally - Ticket Lists, 1966 November 4 (Box 26, Folder 342)
    - Ross, Stanley, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 343)
      Editor of "El Tiempo" newspaper editorials, news clips, correspondence.
    - Rossides, Eugene T. Re: Jewish and Greek Voters, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 344)
    - Route 17 Association, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 345)
    - Rural Citizens, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 346)
    - Scheduling Committee - New Highway Openings, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 347)
    - Security - ID Cards, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 348)
    - Senate Campaign Guidelines by Al Abrams, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 349)
    - Spad, Carl, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 350)
    - Spanish-Speaking Campaign, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 351)
      Recruitment, memos, correspondence.
    - Speakers Bureau - Sample Speeches, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 352)
    - Nelson Rockefeller Appearances - Descriptions of Occasion, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 353)
    - Store Fronts - Location Lists, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 354)
    - Surveys, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 355)
      Polls, Candidate Standing, April 1966, Hudson Valley, August 1966.
    - Sales Tax, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 356)
    - Tufaro, Frank P., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 357)
      Complaint re: construction at State University at Stony Brook.
    - Vote Analyses 1958 and 1962, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 358)
    - Campaign Volunteers, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 359)
    - Watkins, Thomas - "New York Recorder" - New York Daily (Negro), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 360)
    - Weekend Schedules - Duty Roster, 1966 August - September (Box 27, Folder 361)
    - West Indian Association, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - Women's Division - Conference, Memos, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Young New Yorkers for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 364)
    - Young Republican Clubs, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 365)
    - Broome County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 366)
      Yearbook, miscellaneous correspondence.
    - Erie County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 367)
      Correspondence, (Mike Scelsi).
    - Jefferson County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 368)
    - Kings County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 369)
    - Montgomery County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 370)
    - New York County, 1966 July 8 (Box 28, Folder 370.1)
      Correspondence, Time magazine, article about New York County Surrogate and Robert F. Kennedy.
    - Onondaga County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 371)
      County Republican Committee members
    - Richmond County, Suffolk County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 372)
    - Sullivan County, Ulster County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 373)
    - Westchester County, Wyoming County, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 374)
    - Central Region, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 375)
    - Hudson Valley Region, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 376)
    - Long Island Region, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 377)
    - Northern Region, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 378)
    - Western Region, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 379)
    - 1965 Election Voting and Results, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 380)
    - Foch, Allen, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 381)
      "Harlem Grass Roots Committee for re-election of Governor Rockefeller."
    - Arculeo, Angelo, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 382)
      Vice Chairman, Republican City Campaign Committee for the Rockefeller Team.
    - Beauticians (Negro) for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 383)
    - Bridge and Tunnel Operators, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 384)
    - Burns, John, 1966 August 21 (Box 29, Folder 385)
      Chairman, New York State Democratic Chairman Television interview
    - "Captain's Book" - Campaign manual for Election District Captains, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 386)
    - "Captive Nations Week" - Nelson A. Rockefeller Proclamation, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 387)
    - Chiropractors - Letter in Support of Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 388)
    - Clearview Expressway Extension, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 389)
    - Clemmons, Maxwell, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 390)
      Executive Director of Twentieth Century Action Democratic Club in Bedford-Stuyvesant.
    - Colville, Lorraine, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 391)
    - Doormen for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 392)
    - Drafts Awaiting Approval - Letters from Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 393)
    - Editorials Endorsing Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 394)
    - Firemen, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 395)
    - Foreign Language Press Correspondence, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 396)
      C. G. Alexandrides, press aide, New York City campaign.
    - Editorial Endorsements, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 397)
    - Foreign Language Press - Greek, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 398)
    - Foreign Language Press, Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 399)
    - Foreign Language Press - Photos, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 400)
    - Foreign Language Press - Advertising, Contact Lists, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 401)
    - Foreigh Language Radio - German - Ads, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 402)
    - Foreign Language Radio - Italian - Ads, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 403)
    - Foreign Language Radio - Polish, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 404)
    - Foreigh Language Radio - Spanish, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 405)
    - Greek American Committee, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 406)
    - Hampton, Lionel, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 407)
    - Hungarian Publicity, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 408)
    - Italian Publicity Division, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 409)
    - Jarko, D. - Ukraine, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 410)
    - Keefe, Jack - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 411)
    - Labor, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 412)
    - Letter Writing Campaign, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 413)
    - Lewis, Paul S. - Democratic Club of Queens Village, Endorsement, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 414)
    - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 415)
    - Ludwig, Nathan, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 416)
      Kings County Department of Public Works, volunteer.
    - Mangano, Constantino, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 417)
      Democrat in Queens County, volunteer and job seeker.
    - Medicaid Press Release, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 418)
    - Transcript of Rockefeller, O'Conner, and Roosevelt Debate, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 419)
    - Narcotics, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 420)
    - Nationalities, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 421)
    - Negro Vote, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 422)
    - Negro Press Party, Photo, Invitations, 1966 August 24 (Box 30, Folder 423)
    - O'Connor, Frank - Campaign Literature, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 424)
    - Odom, Retha - New York State of Civil Service, Career Development Program, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 425)
    - Perkins, Curtis, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 426)
      Special Consultant on Negro vote memos, reports, news clippings.
    - Picture Taking Schedule - Nelson Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 427)
    - Pinsley, Stanley, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 428)
      Sought money for a Democrats for Nelson A. Rockefeller campaign.
    - Polish Affairs, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 429)
      Memos for Governor's press release on tenth anniversary of the Poznan riots.
    - Radio Campaign Ada Composed by Jack Tinker, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 430)
    - Rent Strike Law, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 431)
      Draft of campaign literature.
    - Research File I, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 432)
      "O'Connor Errors," O'Connor legislative record, Division of Housing and Urban Renewal statistics.
    - Research File II, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 433)
      "Facts" re: New York City, State construction, State aid.
    - Rittersporn, B.A., Jr., I, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 434)
      Voter Canvas Chief, New York City, canvas reports, polling places, memos.
    - Rittersporn, B.A., Jr., II, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 435)
      New York City canvas memos.
    - CLOSED (Box 31, Folder 435A)
    - Roberson, John - Memos, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 436)
    - Robinson, Gilbert A. - Store Front Operations, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 437)
    - Robinson, Jackie, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 438)
      Draft of Nelson A. Rockefeller letter to clergy, National Negro Republican Assembly telegram to O'Connor, National Negro Republican Assembly dinner.
    - Ronan, William J., 1966 (Box 31, Folder 439)
      Memos, draft of Rockefeller speech re: O'Connor political "deal" to be Democrat gubernatorial candidate.
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr., 1966 August 21; October 6 1966 (Box 31, Folder 440)
      Transcripts of WABC TV news conference.
    - Sanders, Howard, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 441)
      Advertising agency, proposed ad campaign, "Governor Rockefeller and the Negro Vote", ("The Deciding Minority").
    - Schaffer, Raymond, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 442)
      Campaign aide, strategy memos.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 443)
      August, September, October, regrets.
    - Scholars Committee, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 444)
      Authorizations by scholars to use their names in campaign literature.
    - Schultz, Dodi, Scott, Alfred University, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 445)
    - Scripts - Radio Ads, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 446)
    - Shipyard Workers, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 447)
    - Songs (Campaign), 1966 (Box 32, Folder 448)
    - Sound Cars, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 449)
    - Spanish-Speaking Division (of campaign), 1966 (Box 32, Folder 450)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 451)
    - Special Interest Groups, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 452)
    - Staten Island, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 453)
    - Storefronts - New York City Leases, Furniture, Insurance, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 454)
    - Television and Radio Ad, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 455)
    - Tire, Dan - New York City Fire Department's Columbia Association Endorsement, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 456)
    - Touchdown Club - Rockefeller Sports Committee Luncheon, 1966 September 26 (Box 32, Folder 457)
    - Edwards, Deighton O. - 26 Assembly District, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 458)
    - Sanitation Workers - John de Lury, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 459)
    - United Negro College Fund - List of Club Members, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 460)
    - Weekly Papers - Releases, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 461)
    - Wisser, Lawrence - Ad Agency, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 462)
    - Workers Compensation Referrals, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 463)
    - Wysocki, Leo, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 464)
      Resigned as Polish Nationalities Division for O'Connor to support Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    - American Jewish Committee Dinner - Nelson A. Rockefeller Speech, 1966 October 22 (Box 33, Folder 465)
    - Canvasing - Ritterspoon Reports, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 466)
    - Coleman Bill Veto - Sabbath Observance, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 467)
    - Conference Call by Rockefeller to Storefronts in New York City - 5 Boroughs, 1966 October 24 (Box 33, Folder 468)
    - Friends of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 October 28 (Box 33, Folder 469)
      Expense report.
    - Jewish Museum, 1966 October 4 (Box 33, Folder 470)
    - Jewish Press, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 471)
    - Joseph Jacobs Organization, Inc. - Advertising, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 472)
    - Literature Distribution, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 473)
    - Manhattan Center Rally, 1966 November 4 (Box 33, Folder 474)
    - Messages - Nelson A. Rockefeller to Jewish Leaders and Causes, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 475)
    - Miscellaneous - Jewish Contacts, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 476)
    - New York Board of Rabbis - Nelson A. Rockefeller Appearance, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 477)
    - Accounting, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 478)
      Payroll changes, petty cash.
    - Radio, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 479)
      Sample questions for Javits and Lefkowitz.
    - Republican City Campaign Committee, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 480)
    - Rosh Hashana, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 481)
      Rockefeller greetings letter to Jewish New Yorkers.
    - Shazar, Zalma - President of Israel, 1966 August 1 (Box 34, Folder 482)
      State visit.
    - Soviet Jewry - Rockefeller Speech and Press Release, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 483)
    - Storefronts - Closing - Memos, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 484)
    - Storefronts - General Cases, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 485)
      Cases, plate glass; Cornell University - student (Thomas A. Russo), paper re: managing Staten Island storefront.
    - Storefronts - Bronx, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 486)
      Memos and correspondense.
    - Storefronts - Broklyn, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 487)
      Lenses, plate glass, memos.
    - Storefronts - Manhattan, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 488)
      Leases, etc.
    - Storefronts - Queens, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 489)
    - Storefronts - Staten Island, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 490)
    - Storefronts Openings and Beach Tours, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 491)
      Memos, press releases, photo reprints and IDs.
    - Storefronts - Typewriter Rentals, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 492)
    - Car Rentals, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 493)
    - Wolk, Asher, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 494)
      Jewish Press division, receptions.
    - World Jewish Congress - Nelson A. Rockefeller Greetings, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 495)
    - Women's Zionist Organization of America - Nelson A. Rockefeller Speech, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 496)
    - Arts and Entertainment Committee of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 497)
      Campaign finance statements.
    - Associates of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 498)
    - Bronx Democrats for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 499)
    - Nelson Rockefeller Calandars, 1966 February (Box 35, Folder 500)
    - Finance Committee - New York Republican State Reports, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 501)
    - Citizens Committee for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 502)
    - Citizens Committee for the Re-Election of the Rockefeller-Wilson Team, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 503)
    - Committee to Elect Good Government Candidates, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 504)
    - Committee for the Nomination of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 505)
    - Republican State Convention Schedule, 1966 September 7-8 (Box 35, Folder 506)
    - County Fairs, Youth Fairs, Agricultural Fairs, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 507)
    - Democratos Hispanos Para Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 508)
    - Democrats and Independents for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 509)
    - Direct Mail Campaign - New York Republican State Committee Report, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 510)
    - Friends of Rockefeller and Wilson, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 511)
      Campaign finance statements, (family and friends).
    - Friends of the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 512)
    - Harlem Democrats for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 513)
    - Harlem Independents for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 514)
    - Independent Voters for Rockefeller and Lefkowitz, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 515)
    - Information Committee for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 516)
    - Labor Committee for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 517)
    - Rockefeller Candidate Statements, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 518)
    - New York Republican State Committee, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 519)
      Campaign filing statement.
    - New York City Committee for the Election of Governor Rockefeller, Lieutenant Governor Wilson, Attorney General Lefkowitz and Hamilton for Comptroller, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 520)
    - Republican City Campaign Committee, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 521)
    - Republican Finance Committee - New York State, 1966 June 30 (Box 36, Folder 522)
    - Republican Finance Committee - New York State, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 523)
    - Saint Albans Democrats for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 524)
      Campaign finance statement.
    - Taxpayers for the Rockefeller Team, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 525)
    - Twentieth Century Action Democrats for Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 526)
    - Women's Division - New York Republican State Committee Report, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 527)
    - Reports and Memos on 1965 Legislators Campaign, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 528)
    - Votes in 1966 Election (Box 37, Folder 529)
    - Invitations, 1966 March-June (Box 37, Folder 530)
    - Invitations I, 1966 July-September (Box 37, Folder 531)
    - Invitations II, 1966 July-September (Box 37, Folder 532)
    - Invitations New York City, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 533)
    - Invitation Recommendations, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 534)
    - Invitation - Speaking Acceptances, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 535)
    - Javits and Nixon Schedules, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 536)
    - Lanigan, Charles T. Schedules, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 537)
    - Lefkowitz - Schedules, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 538)
    - Maps, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 539)
    - Personnel, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 540)
    - Procedures and Scheduling, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 541)
    - Pure Water Bond Act - Resolutions in Support, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 542)
    - Republican Fundraiser Invitations, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 543)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson - Invitations, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 544)
    - Miscellaneous - Requests, Housewives Committee, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 545)
    - Speakers Bureau - Requests, Reports, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 546)
    - Radio and TV - Schedules, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 547)
    - Town Meeting - Schedule, Background Book, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 548)
    - Wilson, Malcolm - Schedule, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 549)
    - YMCA Youth and Work Program - Vocational Service Center, 1966 October (Box 38, Folder 550)
    - Young Republican Clubs, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 551)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 January 15-31 (Box 39, Folder 552)
      Speaking invitations and responces, speeches.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 February 1-14 (Box 39, Folder 553)
      Speaking invitations and responses, speeches.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 February 14-28 (Box 39, Folder 554)
      Speaking invitations and responses, speeches; reading copy (with Nelson A. Rockefeller hanwritten notes), of Nelson A. Rockefeller speech at the 17th Annual Fordhan Law School Alumni Association held in conjunction with the 125th Anniversary of Fordhan University.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 March (Box 39, Folder 555)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 April (Box 39, Folder 556)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 May 1-7 (Box 40, Folder 557)
      Speaking invitations and responses.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 May 8-14 (Box 40, Folder 558)
      Speaking invitation and responses.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 May 15-31 (Box 40, Folder 559)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 June 1-14 (Box 40, Folder 560)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 June 15-30 (Box 41, Folder 561)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 August 1-14 (Box 41, Folder 562)
      Speaking invitation and responses, briefing books on Orange, Hamilton and Wayne Counties.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Schedules, 1966 August 15-22 (Box 41, Folder 563)
      Speaking invitations and responses, briefing book on Chemung County.